The Salem Witch Trials remixed.
The Sisterhood of Night is a mystery, drama,
thriller film directed by Caryn Waechter.
When a teenage girl says she's the victim of a secret network called The Sisterhood of Night, a
quiet suburban town becomes the backdrop for a modern-day Salem witch trial.
Emily Parris, played by Kara Hayward.
Mary Warren, played by Georgie Henley.
Lavinia Hall, played by Olivia DeJonge.
Rose Hall, played by Laura Fraser.
Gordy Gambhir, played by Kal Penn.
Stanley Huang, played by Louis Ozawa.
The Sisterhood of Night is a 2014 American mystery thriller film directed by Caryn Waechter from
a screenplay by Marilyn Fu, based on a 1994 short story by Steven Millhauser.
The film premiered at the 2014 Woodstock Film Festival.
It was released in select theaters and through video on
demand on April 10, 2015, by Freestyle Releasing.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.